

Ankush Sharma(1DS19AE011)

995, 15th cross road, 1st stage Kumaraswamy Layout

+(91)6265577784

Bengaluru, Karnataka

sharmadsaeankush@gmail.com

USN:-1DS19AE011

www.linkedin.com/in/ankush-sharma-0450531b8/

Career Objective

Organized and dependable candidate successful at managing multiple priorities with a positive attitude. Willingness to take on added responsibilities to meet team goals. Reliable candidate studying Aeronautical Engineering seeks a job opportunity to expand skills and gain valuable real-world experience.

Education

	College/School	University/Board	Passing Year	<u>% or</u> <u>CGPA</u>
B.E. (Aeronautical Engineering)	Dayananda Sagar College of Engineering	VTU	Pursuing (2019-2023)	8.5 CGPA
12 th Std	Kendriya Vidyalaya	CBSE	2019	83.2%
10 th Std	Kendriya Vidyalaya	CBSE	2017	10 CGPA

Experience

1. Content Developer (07/2021 - 10/2021) Sanfoundry :- Bengaluru , Karnataka

Created and solve 1000 mcqs for different topics including Analogy, Venn diagrams, Sequence and Series, Coding and Decoding etc. for the AFCAT exam with relevant explanations, which helps many students who are learning from the website.

2. Summer Intern (08/2022-09/2022) Hindustan Aeronautics Limited(HAL):-Bengaluru, Karnataka

Observed and learned various operations in order to manufacture various parts of an aircraft through practical means.

Skills

Technical Competencies	Interpersonal Competencies	
C++	Communication skills	
С	Time management	
Data Structure Algorithm	Documentation review	
Microsoft Excel	Public Speaking	
Microsoft Word	Leadership	
Autodesk Inventor	Analytical Thinking	
CATIA	Fostering Teamwork	

Projects

→To do list

A web app which helps us to keep a check on our to do list and notifies the user about pending activities.

→Optimization of KFm Airfoil

By changing the location of max thickness, we achieved better performance characteristics of KFm airfoil.

Certificates

Geospatial Inputs for Enabling Master Plan Formulation-ISRO Matlab onramp – MathWorks

Mechanical design - **Elite Techno Groups** Catia V5 R21 - **learnmall.in**